[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Залишитись (на ночівлю)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "泊ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Тренування' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "練習"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Прання' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "洗濯"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Прибирання' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "掃除"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Починається' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "始まります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Новий тип, стиль' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新型"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відчиняти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "開きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зал, приміщення' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会場"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Насолоджуватися, розважатися' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "楽しみます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Проспект, головна дорога' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大通り"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вищезазначене, понад, більше' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "以上"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Статуя' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "像"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стрибки на конях' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "競馬"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Динозавр' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "恐竜"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'Будівля' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "建物"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'Знімати(відео), робити(фото), робити репродукцію' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映します"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відображення, картинка, кліп,фото' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映像"
    }
]